Guide to the Eastern Connecticut State University Events Collection 1891-2010 MS 0xx
Eastern Connecticut State University, Publisher
Eastern Connecticut State University Events Collection1891-2010
MS 0xx
3 linear feet (3 boxes)
Eastern Connecticut State University
Eastern Connecticut State University.
The University Events Collection includes information on various campus-wide events. The material in this collection ranges in years from 1891 through the present day.
Provenance
This collection was created by the Archives staff.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
NA
Scope and Content Note
The University Events Collection includes information on various campus-wide events. The type of information varies. It may include programs, invitations, flyers, or general support paperwork as with the annual commencement. The material in this collection ranges in years from 1891 through the present day. Material is chronological with in each series. This collection is added to semi-annually.
Series I - Anniversaries
This series offers information about special celebrations of school anniversaries including the 25th, 50th, 75th, 90th and 100th.
Series II- Arts and Lectures Series
This series contains brochures from the University's Arts and Lectures Series which begun in the fall of 2001. Special guests include authors: John Updike, Maya Angelou, David McCullough; sports legend: Bill Russell; personality: Bill Nye, "the science guy" and musician, Pancho Sanchez.
Series III - Baccalaureate
This series contains programs from the baccalaureate ceremonies which take place on the day of graduation. These ceremonies have been held at the school from 1960-present.
Series IV - Commencement
This series contains information collected from commencement ceremonies dating back to1891, our 1st graduating class, to present day commencement celebrations. The series includes programs, tickets, jubilee reception information, faculty rosters, instructions for graduates and guests as well as information about speakers and special guests.
Series V - Conferences & Cultural Events
This series contains information related to campus-wide conferences and cultural events. Subjects range from International Affairs to Black History. The series covers from 1949 to present.
Series VI - Convocation
The Convocation Series is a collection of programs gathered from Convocation ceremonies from 1984 through the present. Some of the convocations are related to special occasions; however, most are general school convocations, which took place on the first day of the semester.
Series VII - Dedications
This series contains information about the dedication of new buildings on campus including Burr Hall, Shafer Hall and the 1st library building. Materials include guest books, programs and other significant print material related to these occasions.
Series VIII - Groundbreaking
The groundbreaking series contains programs and invitations to ceremonies celebrating the beginning construction of a new building. The series covers the groundbreaking ceremony for the first J. Eugene Smith library in 1968 and continues to the present.
Series IX - Inaugurations
This series contains invitations, programs, and paperwork from the inaugurations of Presidents beginning with President J. Eugene Smith in 1947 and continuing to the present.
Series X - Memorial Services
This series currently contains a sample of programs and invitations for memorial services that have taken place at the school between 1981 and the present.
Series XI - Naming Ceremonies
This series currently contains invitations and programs for the naming of buildings and special rooms from 1999 to the present.
Series XII - Receptions
The Receptions Series includes programs and invitations for various receptions held either on campus, or off campus in honor of faculty, staff, or students from 1988-present. Examples include faculty farewell receptions, emeritus faculty receptions, accounting & honor society receptions as well as the President's Recognition Luncheon.
Series XIII - Retirement & Testimonials
This series contains invitations and programs, personal notes, invitations and programs for events which paid special honor to retiring administrators, faculty or staff members dating from 1945 to the present.
Series XIV - Special Events
This series offers programs and informatio public gatherings, performances or presentations that took place in Shafer Auditorium or another major public space on campus. Events include Choral Festivals, Willimantic Orchestra, dramatic presentations, ECSU Author presentations, and the Connecticut Legislative Breakfast.
Series XV - Special Guests
The Special Guests Series contains programs and information about individual authors, personalities or performers who presented at the school. This material dating from 1984 includes such notable guests as jazz musician Lionel Hampton and Connecticut Governor Lowell Weicker.
Series XVI - University Hour
This series includes information documenting this campus-wide program which encourages the involvement and interaction of the Eastern community. The series which began in 1997 offers a broad range subjects. Past programming has included presentations by faculty, staff, administrators & students covering all disciplines; guest authors & speakers; performances in drama and music and discussions with state legislators and other political figures.
Arrangement
Mixed material labeled “College Events” was updated and organized to create the current University Events Collection which is divided into series by event type or title and arranged alphabetically and chronologically within series.
The files are grouped into 16 series:
Series I - Anniversaries
Series II – Arts and Lectures Series
Series III - Baccalaureate
Series III - Baccalaureate
Series IV - Commencement
Series IV - Commencement
Series IV - Commencement
Series IX - Inaugurations
Series V - Conferences & Cultural Events
Series VI - Convocation
Series VI - Convocation
Series VII - Dedications
Series VIII – Groundbreaking
Series X - Memorial Services
Series XI - Naming Ceremonies
Series XII – Receptions
Series XII – Receptions & Farewells
Series XIII – Retirement-Testimonials
Series XIV - Special Events
Series XIV - Special Events
Series XV - Special Guests
Series XVI - University Hour
Access Points
Subject Topics:
Universities and colleges -- administration.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Notebooks.; Publications.; Press releases.; Audiocassettes.; Fliers.
Other Names:
[OTHER NAMES]
Related Material
Information related to other events at the University can be found in the Alumni Collection, Student Activities Collection, Athletic Department material, and various university publications in the Print Collection. The University Archives has a substantial collection of university archives material and also houses the Connecticut Studies Collection. For more detailed information on these collections please contact the staff member at the reference desk.
Container List
[The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.]
- Series I - Anniversaries
  - Twenty-Fifth (25th), 1914 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Fiftieth (50th), 1939 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - Seventy-Fifth, 1964 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Ninetieth (90th), 1980 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Ninety-first (91st), 1981 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Centennial- Concerts, 1990 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - Centennial- Congratulations, 1989 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - Centennial- Congratulations, 1989 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Centennial- Congratulations, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Centennial- Convocation, 1989 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - Centennial- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - Centennial- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Item 12)
  - Centennial- Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Item 13)
  - Centennial- Homecoming, 1989 (Box 1, Item 14)
  - Centennial- Centennial Recognition Luncheon, 1990 (Box 1, Item 15)
  - Centennial- Commencement, 1990 (Box 1, Item 16)
  - Centennial- Special Events, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Item 17)
  - President Carter’s 10th year, 1998 (Box 1, Item 18)
  - President Carter’s 15th year, 2002 (Box 1, Item 19)
- Series II – Arts and Lectures Series
  - Robben Island Singers; John Updike, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Item 20)
  - Brochure & Flyers, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Item 21)
  - Brochure, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Item 22)
  - Providence Black Repertory Company, Feb 25, 2004 (Box 1, Item 23)
  - Brochure, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Item 24)
  - Brochure, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Item 25)
  - Esmeralda Santiago, Apr 18, 2006 (Box 1, Item 26)
  - Brochure, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Item 27)
  - Brochure, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Item 28)
- Series III - Baccalaureate
  - Class of 1954 (Box 1, Item 29)
  - Class of 1960 (Box 1, Item 30)
  - Class of 1961 (Box 1, Item 31)
  - Class of 1962 (Box 1, Item 32)
  - Class of 1963 (Box 1, Item 33)
  - Class of 1964 (Box 1, Item 34)
  - Class of 1965 (Box 1, Item 35)
  - Class of 1966 (Box 1, Item 36)
  - Class of 1967 (Box 1, Item 37)
  - Class of 1968 (Box 1, Item 38)
  - Class of 1969 (Box 1, Item 39)
- Series III - Baccalaureate
  - Class of 1985 (Box 1, Item 40)
  - Class of 1989 (Box 1, Item 41)
  - Class of 1990 (Box 1, Item 42)
  - Class of 1991 (Box 1, Item 43)
  - Class of 1992 (Box 1, Item 44)
  - Class of 1993 (Box 1, Item 45)
  - Class of 1994 (Box 1, Item 46)
  - Class of 1996 (Box 1, Item 47)
  - Class of 1997 (Box 1, Item 48)
  - Class of 1999 (Box 1, Item 49)
  - Class of 2000 (Box 1, Item 50)
  - Class of 2003 (Box 1, Item 51)
  - Class of 2004 (Box 1, Item 52)
  - Class of 2005 (Box 1, Item 53)
  - Class of 2006- K. Bedini (Box 1, Item 54)
  - Class of 2008- C. DeAngelis (Box 1, Item 55)
- Series IV - Commencement
  - Class of 1891 (Box 1, Item 56)
  - Class of 1899 (Box 1, Item 57)
  - Class of 1905 (Box 1, Item 58)
  - Class of 1908 (Box 1, Item 59)
  - Class of 1912 (Box 1, Item 60)
  - Class of 1913 (Box 1, Item 61)
  - Class of 1914 (Box 1, Item 62)
  - Class of 1915 (Box 1, Item 63)
  - Class of 1922 (Box 1, Item 64)
  - Class of 1926 (Box 1, Item 65)
  - Class of 1927 (Box 1, Item 66)
  - Class of 1929 (Box 1, Item 67)
  - Class of 1930 (Box 1, Item 68)
  - Class of 1933 (Box 1, Item 69)
  - Class of 1935 (Box 1, Item 70)
  - Class of 1938 (Box 1, Item 71)
  - Class of 1939 (Box 1, Item 72)
  - Class of 1940 (Box 1, Item 73)
  - Class of 1947 (Box 1, Item 74)
  - Class of 1948 (Box 1, Item 75)
  - Class of 1949 (Box 1, Item 76)
  - Class of 1950 (Box 1, Item 77)
  - Class of 1951 (Box 1, Item 78)
  - Class of 1952 (Box 1, Item 79)
- Series IV - Commencement
  - Class of 1953 (Box 1, Item 80)
  - Class of 1954 (Box 1, Item 81)
  - Class of 1956 (Box 1, Item 82)
  - Class of 1957 (Box 1, Item 83)
  - Class of 1958 (Box 1, Item 84)
  - Class of 1959 (Box 1, Item 85)
  - Class of 1960 (Box 1, Item 86)
  - Class of 1961 (Box 1, Item 87)
  - Class of 1962 (Box 1, Item 88)
  - Class of 1963 (Box 1, Item 89)
  - Class of 1964 (Box 1, Item 90)
  - Class of 1965 (Box 1, Item 91)
  - Class of 1966 (Box 1, Item 92)
  - Class of 1967 (Box 1, Item 93)
  - Class of 1968 (Box 1, Item 94)
  - Class of 1969 (Box 1, Item 95)
  - Class of 1970 (Box 1, Item 96)
  - Class of 1971 (Box 1, Item 97)
  - Class of 1972 (Box 1, Item 98)
  - Class of 1973 (Box 1, Item 99)
  - Class of 1974 (Box 1, Item 100)
  - Class of 1975 (Box 1, Item 101)
  - Class of 1976 (Box 1, Item 102)
  - Class of 1977 (Box 1, Item 103)
  - Class of 1978 (Box 1, Item 104)
  - Class of 1979 (Box 1, Item 105)
  - Class of 1979- Speaker (Box 1, Item 106)
  - Class of 1980 (Box 1, Item 107)
  - Class of 1981 (Box 1, Item 108)
  - Class of 1982 (Box 1, Item 109)
  - Class of 1983 (Box 1, Item 110)
  - Class of 1984 (Box 1, Item 111)
  - Class of 1984 - Speaker (Box 1, Item 112)
  - Class of 1985 (Box 1, Item 113)
  - Class of 1986 (Box 1, Item 114)
  - Class of 1987 (Box 1, Item 115)
  - Class of 1987- Speaker (Box 1, Item 116)
  - Class of 1988 (Box 1, Item 117)
  - Class of 1989 (Box 1, Item 118)
  - Class of 1989 - Speaker (Box 1, Item 119)
  - Class of 1990 (Box 1, Item 120)
  - Class of 1991 (Box 1, Item 121)
  - Class of 1991- Speakers (Box 1, Item 122)
- Series IV - Commencement
  - Class of 1992 (Box 1, Item 123)
  - Class of 1992- Correspondence/Speaker (Box 1, Item 124)
  - Class of 1993 (Box 1, Item 125)
  - Class of 1993- Correspondence (Box 1, Item 126)
  - Class of 1994 (Box 1, Item 127)
  - Class of 1994- Correspondence (Box 1, Item 128)
  - Class of 1995 (Box 1, Item 129)
  - Class of 1996 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Class of 1996- Correspondence (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Class of 1997 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Class of 1997- Speakers (Box 2, Item 4)
  - Class of 1998 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Class of 1999 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - Class of 1999-Correspondence/Speaker (Box 2, Item 7)
  - Class of 2000 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - Class of 2001 (Box 2, Item 9)
  - Class of 2002 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - Class of 2002- Correspondence/Speaker (Box 2, Item 11)
  - Official Statement of the Governor, 2002 (Box 2, Item 12)
  - Class of 2003 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - Class of 2003- Speaker (Box 2, Item 14)
  - Official Statement of the Governor, 2003 (Box 2, Item 15)
  - Class of 2003- Jamaica Ceremony (Box 2, Item 16)
  - Class of 2004 (Box 2, Item 17)
  - Class of 2005 (Box 2, Item 18)
  - Class of 2006 (Box 2, Item 19)
  - Press, 2006 (Box 2, Item 20)
  - Class of 2007 (Box 2, Item 21)
  - Class of 2008- Governor (Box 2, Item 22)
  - Class of 2008- Programs (Box 2, Item 23)
  - Winter Reception, Dec 17, 1993 (Box 2, Item 24)
  - Winter Reception, 1994 (Box 2, Item 25)
  - Winter Reception, 1995 (Box 2, Item 26)
  - Winter Reception, 1996 (Box 2, Item 27)
  - Winter Reception, 1998 (Box 2, Item 28)
  - Winter Reception, 1999 (Box 2, Item 29)
  - Winter Reception, 2000 (Box 2, Item 30)
  - Winter Reception, 2001 (Box 2, Item 31)
  - Winter Reception, 2002 (Box 2, Item 32)
  - Winter Reception, 2004 (Box 2, Item 33)
  - Winter Reception, 2005 (Box 2, Item 34)
  - Winter Reception, 2006 (Box 2, Item 35)
- Series V - Conferences & Cultural Events
  - International Relations, 1949 (Box 2, Item 36)
  - Human Understanding, 1951 (Box 2, Item 37)
  - Music from Israel, 1953 (Box 2, Item 38)
  - World Affairs, 1954 (Box 2, Item 39)
  - India, 1955 (Box 2, Item 40)
  - Freedom Day, 1960 (Box 2, Item 41)
  - Human Relations, 1962 (Box 2, Item 42)
  - All-College, 1963 (Box 2, Item 43)
  - Generation in Crisis, 1963 (Box 2, Item 44)
  - Education of American Teachers, 1964 (Box 2, Item 45)
  - Noble School, 1964 (Box 2, Item 46)
  - Crime and Delinquency, 1966 (Box 2, Item 47)
  - The Arts and Humanities, 1967 (Box 2, Item 48)
  - Institutional Goals, 1977 (Box 2, Item 49)
  - Connecticut Council for Teachers of English, 1978 (Box 2, Item 50)
  - Threshold (Agency on Aging), 1978 (Box 2, Item 51)
  - Computer Fair II, 1983 (Box 2, Item 52)
  - American Name Society, 1984 (Box 2, Item 53)
  - Annual Computing Conference, Mar 11, 1989 (Box 2, Item 54)
  - Latin American Awareness, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Item 55)
  - Cultural Events brochure, Fall 1994 (Box 2, Item 56)
  - Global Perspectives, Spring 1994 (Box 2, Item 57)
  - Academic Computing Conference, Apr 4, 1998 (Box 2, Item 58)
  - CSU Annual Research Conference, Oct 16, 1999 (Box 2, Item 59)
  - Contemporary African Issues, 2001 (Box 2, Item 60)
  - CSU Academic Computing Conference, Apr 6, 2002 (Box 2, Item 61)
  - 2002 Peace Conference, Nov 9, 2002 (Box 2, Item 62)
  - Assessment Summit, Black History, 2003 (Box 2, Item 63)
  - Arts & Sciences Research Conference & Exhibition, Apr 24, 2006 (Box 2, Item 64)
- Series VI - Convocation
  - Parent's Day, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Item 65)
  - Oct 13, 1981 (Box 2, Item 66)
  - Honoring Lionel Hampton, 1984 (Box 2, Item 67)
  - CSU Faculty, 1985 (Box 2, Item 68)
  - Centennial, 1989 (Box 2, Item 69)
  - Aug 24, 1994 (Box 2, Item 70)
  - Sep 5, 1995 (Box 2, Item 71)
  - Aug 28, 1996 (Box 2, Item 72)
  - Aug 27, 1997 (Box 2, Item 73)
  - Aug 26, 1998 (Box 2, Item 74)
  - Aug 25, 1999 (Box 2, Item 75)
  - Sep 1, 2000 (Box 2, Item 76)
- Series VI - Convocation
  - Aug 31, 2001 (Box 2, Item 77)
  - Aug 30, 2002 (Box 2, Item 78)
  - Aug 29, 2003 (Box 2, Item 79)
  - Aug 27, 2004 (Box 2, Item 80)
  - Aug 26, 2005 (Box 2, Item 81)
  - Aug 31, 2007 (Box 2, Item 82)
- Series VII - Dedications
  - Burr Hall, 1940 (Box 2, Item 83)
  - New Admin/Classroom, 1949 (Box 2, Item 84)
  - Shafer Hall, 1949 (Box 2, Item 85)
  - Shafer Hall- Guestbook, 1949 (Box 2, Item 86)
  - J. Eugene Smith Library I, 1971 (Box 2, Item 87)
  - J. Eugene Smith Library I - Guestbook, 1971 (Box 2, Item 88)
  - Sports Center, 1973 (Box 2, Item 89)
  - Samson Occum Hall, 1984 (Box 2, Item 90)
  - David M. Roth Center for CT Studies, 1987 (Box 2, Item 91)
  - Noble Hall, 1992 (Box 2, Item 92)
  - New Classroom Building (Webb), 1992 (Box 2, Item 93)
  - Baseball Complex, 1998 (Box 2, Item 94)
  - RVA(Mead), RVB(Neijadlik) & Admissions Building, 1999 (Box 2, Item 95)
  - J. Eugene Smith Library II (NEW), 1999 (Box 2, Item 96)
  - Paul E. Johnson Sr. Community Conference Room, 1999 (Box 2, Item 97)
  - Frederick A. Gelsi, Leslie T. Young Hall, 2002 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - SRV I (Constitution Hall), 2004 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Child and Family Development Resource Center, 2006 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Student Center (Renovation), 2007 (Box 3, Item 4)
- Series VIII – Groundbreaking
  - New Admin/Class. Bldg., Laying of Cornerstone, 1946 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - J.Eugene Smith Library I, 1968 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Sports Center, 1971 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Student Center, 1974 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Maintenance Building, 1984 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - New Classroom Building, 1989 (Box 3, Item 6)
  - Baseball Complex, 1995 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - J. Eugene Smith Library II, 1995 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - Neijadlik Hall (RVB), 1997 (Box 3, Item 9)
  - Administration Building (Gelsi/Young), 2001 (Box 3, Item 10)
  - South Residential Village, 2003 (Box 3, Item 11)
  - Child and Family Center, 2004 (Box 3, Item 12)
  - Science Building, Feb 18, 2006 (Box 3, Item 13)
- Series IX - Inaugurations
  - President Smith - Invitations (3) Programs(2), Nov 23, 1947 (Box 3, Item 14)
  - President Smith, press release, 1947 (Box 3, Item 15)
  - President Charles- Programs (2), Apr 30, 1967 (Box 3, Item 16)
  - President Charles- Inaugural Address, Apr 30, 1967 (Box 3, Item 17)
  - President Webb-Inaugural Address, ticket (1), Mar 5, 1972 (Box 3, Item 18)
  - President Carter- Invitations (3) & Schedule, Sep 29, 1988 (Box 3, Item 19)
  - President Carter-Programs (2), Sep 29, 1988 (Box 3, Item 20)
  - President Carter- Inaugural Address, Sep 29, 1988 (Box 3, Item 21)
  - David G. Carter Sr., Chancellor CSU, 2006 (Box 3, Item 22)
  - President Nuñez-Invitations, 2007 (Box 3, Item 23)
  - President Nuñez- Programs, 2007 (Box 3, Item 24)
  - President Nuñez- Historical handout, 2007 (Box 3, Item 25)
- Series X - Memorial Services
  - Edward J. Mulligan, 1981 (Box 3, Item 26)
  - Hermann Beckert, 1985 (Box 3, Item 27)
  - David M. Roth, 1986 (Box 3, Item 28)
  - Four ECSU Students, 1991 (Box 3, Item 29)
  - Kerry Lynn Hyldreth, 1992 (Box 3, Item 30)
  - Bernice Niejadlik, 1999 (Box 3, Item 31)
  - Jean H. Thoresen, 2000 (Box 3, Item 32)
  - Bertram W. Wilson, Jr., 2002 (Box 3, Item 33)
  - Bertram W. Wilson, Jr. (Media), 2002 (Box 3, Item 34)
- Series XI - Naming Ceremonies
  - Charles R. Webb Hall, 1999 (Box 3, Item 35)
  - Dr. Arthur L. Johnson Unity Center, 2000 (Box 3, Item 36)
  - Sophie L Jenkins Living Room, 2000 (Box 3, Item 37)
  - Foster Clock Tower, 2001 (Box 3, Item 38)
  - Mead Hall, Wood Hall, Niejadlik Hall, 2001 (Box 3, Item 39)
  - Thomas Nevers Varsity Soccer-Lacrosse Field, 2001 (Box 3, Item 40)
- Series XII – Receptions & Farewells
  - Faculty Reception, 1905 (Box 3, Item 41)
  - Farewell- Michael Jones, 1989 (Box 3, Item 42)
  - Emeritus Faculty, 1995 (Box 3, Item 43)
  - Farewell- Lucille R. Wooding, 1995 (Box 3, Item 44)
  - Emeritus Faculty, 1996 (Box 3, Item 45)
  - Farewell- Roy H. Merolli, 1996 (Box 3, Item 46)
  - Farewell- Stanley F. Battle, 1998 (Box 3, Item 47)
  - President’s Recognition Luncheon, 1998 (Box 3, Item 48)
  - President’s Recognition Luncheon, 1999 (Box 3, Item 49)
  - Emeritus Faculty, 2000 (Box 3, Item 50)
- Series XII – Receptions
  - Farewell- Patricia Terry, 2000 (Box 3, Item 51)
  - President’s Recognition Luncheon, 2000 (Box 3, Item 52)
  - Farewell- John Listro and Lyle Yorks, 2000 (Box 3, Item 53)
  - Farewell- Kirk Peters, 2001 (Box 3, Item 54)
  - Farewell- Will Hare, 2001 (Box 3, Item 55)
  - Farewell- David Hemenway, 2001 (Box 3, Item 56)
  - President’s Recognition Luncheon, 2001 (Box 3, Item 57)
  - Emeriti Faculty, 2002 (Box 3, Item 58)
  - President’s Recognition Luncheon, 2002 (Box 3, Item 59)
  - Farewell- Barbara R. Eshoo, 2003 (Box 3, Item 60)
  - Farewell- Tina Fu, 2003 (Box 3, Item 61)
  - Professor of the Year-Rhona Free, Dec 14, 2004 (Box 3, Item 62)
  - Farewell-Beverly Anderson, 2004 (Box 3, Item 63)
  - Farewell-Jeffery Trawick-Smith I, 2004 (Box 3, Item 64)
- Series XIII – Retirement-Testimonials
  - Margaret C. Hurley, Jun 27, 1945 (Box 3, Item 65)
  - J. Eugene Smith, Jan 15, 1966 (Box 3, Item 66)
  - Robert Wickware, May 3, 1974 (Box 3, Item 67)
  - Francis E. Geissler, 4-5 February 1977 (Box 3, Item 68)
  - Hermann Beckert, Jun 1, 1979 (Box 3, Item 69)
  - Frank P. Bodurtha, Mar 24, 1981 (Box 3, Item 70)
  - C. Francis Willey, Apr 9, 1983 (Box 3, Item 71)
  - Cora Johnson Moore, Sep 29, 1984 (Box 3, Item 72)
  - Pat Muldoon, Jun 18, 1985 (Box 3, Item 73)
  - President Charles R. Webb Jr., Mar 25, 1988 (Box 3, Item 74)
  - Margaret S. Wilson, Apr 1, 1989 (Box 3, Item 75)
  - Ronald V. Stephens, Nov 22, 1991 (Box 3, Item 76)
  - Retirees (20), Feb 20, 1992 (Box 3, Item 77)
  - Salvatore P. Ternullo, Mar 5, 1994 (Box 3, Item 78)
  - Ray Delude and Richard Pepin, Dec 20, 1996 (Box 3, Item 79)
  - Owen Peagler, Oct 19, 1998 (Box 3, Item 80)
  - Sharlene Peter, Oct 27, 1999 (Box 3, Item 81)
  - John S. Berkett, Dec 12, 2000 (Box 3, Item 82)
  - Retirees (group), May 27, 2003 (Box 3, Item 83)
  - Chief Lewis J. Perry, Jr., Aug 16, 2005 (Box 3, Item 84)
- Series XIV - Special Events
  - President’s Tea, 1964 (Box 3, Item 85)
  - Intercollegiate Choral Festival, Apr 19, 1979 (Box 3, Item 86)
  - Intercollegiate Choral Festival, Apr 21, 1981 (Box 3, Item 87)
  - First Connecticut State College Professional Conference, Nov 21, 1981 (Box 3, Item 88)
  - Intercollegiate Choral Festival, Apr 19, 1983 (Box 3, Item 89)
- Series XIV - Special Events
  - Interuniversity Choral Festival, Apr 9, 1985 (Box 3, Item 90)
  - The Manhattan Spring Quartet, Dec 4, 1986 (Box 3, Item 91)
  - The Manhattan Spring Quartet, Apr 20, 1989 (Box 3, Item 92)
  - Annual Choral Festival, Apr 25, 1989 (Box 3, Item 93)
  - Willimantic Orchestra, 1989 (Box 3, Item 94)
  - Willimantic Orchestra, 1990 (Box 3, Item 95)
  - CSU Choral Festival, Apr 26, 1994 (Box 3, Item 96)
  - Shostakovich, 1995 (Box 3, Item 97)
  - CT Jazz Confederation, 1997 (Box 3, Item 98)
  - Legislative Breakfast, 2001 (Box 3, Item 99)
  - 2001 Young Writers Regional Award Ceremony, Apr 23, 2001 (Box 3, Item 100)
  - President’s Recognition Luncheon, Oct 30, 2001 (Box 3, Item 101)
  - Legislative Breakfast, 2002 (Box 3, Item 102)
  - Young Writers Regional Awards, 2003 (Box 3, Item 103)
  - Faculty Luncheon, 2002 (Box 3, Item 104)
  - September 11th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 3, Item 105)
  - Supreme Court on Tour, 2003 (Box 3, Item 106)
  - The Reception for Mauritania, undated (Box 3, Item 107)
  - Rhona Free Award, 2004 (Box 3, Item 108)
  - Legislative Breakfast, 2004 (Box 3, Item 109)
  - University Crest, 2005 (Box 3, Item 110)
  - University Crest, Apr 12, 2005 (Box 3, Item 111)
  - Life after Brown, 2005 (Box 3, Item 112)
  - A Night With the Beijing Opera, Sept 29-Oct2, 2005 (Box 3, Item 113)
  - Celebrating Leadership, Mar 23, 2006 (Box 3, Item 114)
  - Regional Ceremonies-CSU-IMPAC Young Writers, Apr 17, 2006 (Box 3, Item 115)